<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://blog.devs.beer/blog</id>
    <title>LoneDev's Blog Blog</title>
    <updated>2021-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://blog.devs.beer/blog"/>
    <subtitle>LoneDev's Blog Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://blog.devs.beer/img/favicon.png</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of ItemsAdder]]></title>
        <id>future-of-itemsadder</id>
        <link href="https://blog.devs.beer/blog/future-of-itemsadder"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ItemsAdder]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>ItemsAdder</h2><p><a href="https://www.spigotmc.org/resources/73355/">ItemsAdder</a> is my most successful product. It&#x27;s a plugin for <a href="https://www.spigotmc.org/">Spigot</a> servers which allows admins to extend the game without modding the client.</p><h2>First days</h2><p>The plugin was published initially on 2016 and was called <strong>NewItems</strong>, it was one of my very first Java projects and I was a newbie on Spigot development.<br/>
I abandoned the old project after a year or so due to personal life, but then I picked it back up and started working on the very new version which ended up begin renamed ItemsAdder. As you know this version has more features, has a totally different structure and allows to achieve extreme customization of the game.</p><h2>Current days</h2><p>I didn&#x27;t expect this much fame for that single product, the <a href="https://bstats.org/plugin/bukkit/ItemsAdder/7023">max peak</a> of servers which use ItemsAdder amounts to <strong>1097 max online servers</strong> and <strong>3800 max players</strong> enjoying the plugin.<br/>
ItemsAdder is in the <a href="https://i.imgur.com/m3edZ8T.png">top 3</a> of the best voted paid Spigot plugins to this date, which is unbelievable, a plugin published in 2019 managed to reach the top 3 in 2 years while the forum itself is online since 2012.</p><p>Currently my main efforts are to maintain the most stable and optimized code as possible because this plugin is used on servers with more than 100 players connected, performance is a priority in these cases.</p><p>The most difficult task is to give support to customers because a lot of them find it easier to contact me without reading the official tutorials nor asking to the other community members and this sadly cuts a lot of the development time.
I&#x27;d love to spend more time on actually coding the plugin.<br/>
Sadly most of them blackmail me with 1 star reviews which is making this situation really hard to maintain in the long term. </p><h2>The future</h2><p>Back in the day I rushed a lot of ItemsAdder features initial planning, this resulted in non-balanced default stats and gameplay, this is why I&#x27;m currently working with some friends to rebalance the default items pack and provide a better gameplay.<br/>
This is a very long task due to the fact that this plugin offers more than 500 default items/materials/blocks but I&#x27;ll do my best to release an updated pack before mid 2022.<br/>
I also plan to hook into the Minecraft gameplay itself and fix all the unbalanced features of the vanilla gameplay. Sadly this game has a lot of flaws which allow users to <a href="https://www.speedrun.com/mc/run/zq13899m">speedrun it in no time</a>.</p><p>One of the last important tasks I have scheduled is to find a proper way to avoid spamming customers which are contacting me everyday to ask basic questions. Right now I have no solution as this is the problem every developer has with this community.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>LoneDev</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/lonedev6</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimize Minecraft client]]></title>
        <id>optimize-minecraft</id>
        <link href="https://blog.devs.beer/blog/optimize-minecraft"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to optimize it]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>How to optimize it</h2><h3>1. Downloading Fabric</h3><p>First you have to <a href="https://fabricmc.net/use/">download</a> <strong>Fabric</strong> and install it.<br/>
Click on the &quot;<strong>Download installer</strong>&quot; button:</p><p><img src="imgs/1.png"/></p><h3>2. Edit the profile folder (optional step)</h3><p>Click on &quot;<strong>installations</strong>&quot;, then press on &quot;<strong>edit</strong>&quot; under the &quot;<strong>Fabric</strong>&quot; installation.</p><p><img src="imgs/3.png"/></p><p>Change the folder to a new one, for example I created a new profile folder called <code>Fabric</code> inside <code>.minecraft</code>.</p><p><img src="imgs/4.png"/></p><h3>3. Install the optimization mod</h3><p>Download the mod <a href="https://www.curseforge.com/minecraft/modpacks/fabulously-optimized/files/3559545">here</a></p><p>Open the zip and extract the folders <code>mods</code> and <code>config</code> inside your <code>.minecraft</code> folder (or inside the <strong>Fabric</strong> profile folder).</p><h3>4. Run Fabric</h3>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>LoneDev</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/lonedev6</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>