<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://blog.devs.beer/blog</id>
    <title>LoneDev's Blog Blog</title>
    <updated>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://blog.devs.beer/blog"/>
    <subtitle>LoneDev's Blog Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://blog.devs.beer/img/favicon.png</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plans for the year 2024]]></title>
        <id>2024-plans</id>
        <link href="https://blog.devs.beer/blog/2024-plans"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wasting time]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Wasting time</h2><p>I realized over the past year that I spend a lot of time on various tasks during my day.</p><h3>Building Maven modules</h3><p>Building Maven modules of <strong>ItemsAdder</strong> takes me around 30 seconds at the moment.<br/>
I bought my PC in 2015, and my i7-4790k might be nearing its end, which is the reason I decided to build a new PC with the most recent i9-14900KF.<br/>
This should definitely speed up the build time as I recompile my projects hundreds of times each day during development.<br/></p><p>:::info Note for the super gigachad Java reddit mods devs 🤓☝<br/>
No. Hotreload is not an option due to how my Maven setup works. Lot of my NMS classes are dynamically loaded and hotreload always fails due to the custom hooks.<br/>
Another limitation of hotreload is the fact that new methods and new properties break the hotreload, so it&#x27;s pretty useless at this stage, most of my values are set in the <code>config.yml</code>, so I can easily swap them. Hotreload is not useful for my projects.
:::</p><h3>Answering support requests</h3><h4>My current workflow to handle support requests</h4><ul><li>check if the issue is readable and understandable</li><li>check if it has every information needed for me to reproduce the issue on my machine</li><li>setup a clean test server</li><li>start the client (multiple if needed)</li><li>setup ItemsAdder as the customer did</li><li>try to reproduce the issue</li></ul><p>This whole task requires from 30 to 1 hour, depends on the gravity of complexity of the issue.<br/>
If the issue is reproducible, then I proceed to check the cause of the issue.</p><p>The cause of the issue is bind to how the game works, how another plugin works, how my plugin works.<br/>
In each of these cases, I have to spend a lot of time documenting how to reproduce the issue to fix it and make sure it will never appear again.</p><p>In some cases I have to reimplement a fix for EVERY implementation/version of the server and for every client version (lot of servers are sadly using <strong>ViaVersion</strong>).</p><h5>Servers using unstable stuff</h5><p>A lot of servers are currently using solutions like ViaVersion+ViaBackwards and Geyser.<br/>
These hacks are a nightmare to handle because they make the gameplay unpredictable due to how each client handles stuff in a very different way. This causes confusion both on the customer and on the players due to how some glitches are introduced in the game.<br/>
My opinion is that there is no real advantage to continue supporting Geyser due to how different the Java client behaves compared to the Bedrock client.<br/></p><h6>Solution</h6><p>I have no solution for now other than continuing to avoid supporting Geyser.</p><h5>Invalid support requests</h5><p>As I said previously in one of my old blog posts: I waste ton of time organizing support requests on Github.<br/>
Currently, 31% (<a href="https://github.com/PluginBugs/Issues-ItemsAdder/issues?q=label%3A%22verdict%3A+invalid%22%2C%22verdict%3A+can%27t+reproduce%22%2C%22outdated%3A+server%22%2C%22outdated%3A+dependency%22%2C%22outdated%3A+plugin%22%2C%22outdated%3A+client%22%2C%22status%3A+need+more+info%22%2C%22verdict%3A+can%27t+reproduce%22%2C%22verdict%3A+misconfigured%22+">1012</a>/3270) of the Github issues pages of <strong>ItemsAdder</strong> are invalid (data obtained on 2024-Jan-23).<br/></p><p>This requires me to actually provide an explanation to the customer, causing both frustration on my side and on theirs, because most of them don&#x27;t accept their issue to be closed without an instant fix.<br/></p><h6>Solution</h6><p>I have no solution for now other than continuing to handle reviews this way.</p><h4>Bad reviews</h4><p>Some customers are very stubborn and continue bumping threads even if the issue cannot be reproduced, they are running old versions of the plugin or server, they are using unofficial forks or even if they don&#x27;t provide any information about the issue other than &quot;it not work, pls help&quot;.<br/>
This results in 1 star reviews which have the only purpose of trying to get my attention and prioritize their support requests.</p><p>I spend half of the 2023 ignoring bad reviews instead of prioritizing these customers, as it&#x27;s disrespectful both for me and for the other patient customers.<br/>
Instead, I&#x27;m concentrating on making my products better and helping customers which correctly provide information about their issue.<br/>
During this initial period of time I noticed a very large increase in the customers amount and, I&#x27;m sure the trust of customers is increased too.<br/>
Good reviewers will always come due to the quality of the plugin updates.</p><h6>Solution</h6><p>Ignore the bad lazy reviews and concentrate on making the plugin better.</p><h3>License checking</h3><p>Currently, BuiltByBit has no easy way for me to check if a user purchased a resource using their payment email, meanwhile PayPal and Stripe allows me to do that by scraping my own email notifications.<br/>
So for now, I am forced to manually verify purchased on my forum and on the Discord server for these customers.</p><h6>Solution</h6><p>The next thing to do is find a way to automate that also for people who are buying using BuiltByBit.</p><h3>Lack of staff members</h3><p>The sad reality of my business is that the staff members that I hire are always losing interest after a few weeks or during the first months.<br/>
This is something I had to face since 2019, the first time when I started hiring staff members.<br/>
This is a clear proof of how frustrating and hard is to deal with customers in this business type.</p><h6>Solution</h6><p>An idea I had during this year was to teach an AI how to answer the general support request questions, as most of them are generic questions who have answer in the plugin wiki/docs.<br/>
I&#x27;m not really into the idea of replacing humans with AI, but this is a very frustrating and repetitive task, so I don&#x27;t see any issue on doing that.</p><h3>Beta testing team lack of response</h3><p>The beta testing team for my plugins is unresponsive, unmotivated, and most of the beta builds I send are not even downloaded.<br/>
This is a big issue since it vanishes completely the purpose of having a selected set of members who test my plugins to avoid the whole customers to experience issues.</p><h6>Solution</h6><p>Post beta builds on a public accessible place, so people can autonomously access the builds and test them.<br/>
I will obviously put a big disclaimer to let people know about the risks of each specific beta build.</p><h3>Difficulty for customers to find my products</h3><p>Currently, I sell my products on multiple platforms: SpigotMC, BuiltByBit, Polymart.<br/>
This leads to confusion because they can&#x27;t easily peruse my entire product catalog.</p><h6>Solution</h6><p>I decided to create a <a href="https://plugins.devs.beer/">simple website</a> that provides a comprehensive list of all my products across all platforms in a single location.</p><h2>New Spigot plugins projects</h2><p>I&#x27;m starting to work on new ideas and publish them. The new Minecraft updates provide some interesting features I&#x27;m taking advantage of.<br/>
Some clear examples are <a href="https://builtbybit.com/resources/rpgdrops.35127/">RPGDrops</a> and <a href="https://builtbybit.com/resources/chestpreview.35126/">ChestPreview</a>.</p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/8-jhGEJFi6I?si=eFMYLV7KbzTataHU" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share"></iframe><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/dXtPnJ5qiNo?si=BUQcxkmpTaZUjiiG" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share"></iframe><h2>Other projects</h2><h3>Narcolepsy - horror videogame</h3><p>This year, thanks to the new PC, I plan to finally release a working alpha version of my upcoming co-op horror game which I&#x27;ve been delaying for the last 7 years due to the lack of time and motivation.</p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/videoseries?si=LQDDIyXl1V8aYPVP&amp;amp;list=PLjFS6vNIvB8gFri-uvJNvGQtxeFSNN8EK" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share"></iframe><h4>Issues with the project</h4><p>The main issues with this project are the fact that <strong>Unity 3D</strong> team is constantly messing up with the engine on each update, causing a very slow experience. With the new PC I hope to be able to work faster as I waste a ton of time building the project due to how slow the whole <strong>Unity 3D</strong> engine works.<br/>
Another solution is to completely discard <strong>Unity 3D</strong> and move to another engine or make my own engine, since the game uses <strong>PS1</strong> styled graphics, so no fancy RTX Unreal Engine v666 is needed for this kind of projects.</p><h2>Conclusion</h2><p>Wishing everyone a great year in 2024 and thank you for being a part of my community.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>LoneDev</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/lonedev6</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synology auto backup PC on night]]></title>
        <id>synology-auto-backup-pc</id>
        <link href="https://blog.devs.beer/blog/synology-auto-backup-pc"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Introduction</h2><p>I&#x27;ve always felt the need to backup my PC automatically without worrying about it.<br/>
I also wanted to find a way to restore my PC disks without too much work in case one of them failed someday.<br/></p><p>I searched a lot online for a proper solution for this but I couldn&#x27;t find anything which was <strong>plug &amp; play</strong> (&amp; forget).</p><h2>My solution</h2><p>I bought a Synology NAS which supports <a href="https://www.synology.com/en-global/dsm/feature/active_backup_business">Active Backup for Business</a>.<br/>
The only limitation is that this backup system lacks of a feature to get the PC turned on automatically before backup and turned off after backup, so I had to make an hack.</p><p>:::warning
This tutorial was tested on <a href="https://www.synology.com/it-it/products/DS220+">DS220+</a> and on a PC with <strong>Windows 10</strong>.
:::</p><h3>1. Setting up the Active Backup for Business app</h3><p>First of all you have to download it from the <strong>Package Center</strong>.<br/></p><p><img src="imgs/1.png"/></p><p>Then you can access it through the apps menu.</p><p><img src="imgs/2.png"/></p><p>Now add a new device, in this case your PC.</p><p><img src="imgs/3.png"/></p><p>Create a backup task for the Windows disk selecting <code>System volume</code> as type.</p><p><img src="imgs/4.png"/></p><p>Schedule it to be ran at 3.20AM each Monday.</p><p><img src="imgs/4_2.png"/></p><p>Create a backup task for your other disks selecting <code>Customized volume</code> as type.</p><p><img src="imgs/5.png"/></p><p>Schedule them/it to be ran at 3.20AM each Monday.</p><p><img src="imgs/4_2.png"/></p><h3>2. Setting up the Active Backup for Business Agent on Windows</h3><p>You also have to download the <a href="https://kb.synology.com/DSM/help/ActiveBackupBusinessAgent/activebackupbusinessagent">Agent app for Windows</a>, follow their installation tutorial.</p><h3>3. Scheduling automatic startup/shutdown of your Synology</h3><p>Open the <code>Control panel</code>, then open <code>Hardware &amp; Power</code>.<br/>
Now create a new <code>Startup</code> task and set it to be executed at 3AM. We want to make sure the Synology NAS is turned on completely before backups.<br/>
Create a new <code>Shut Down</code> task and set it to be executed at 7AM. We want make sure all backups are finished and let the NAS do its own things if needed (optimizing the drive, deleting old backups etc).</p><p><img src="imgs/6.png"/></p><h3>4. Scheduling automatic startup of your PC</h3><p>Open the <code>Control panel</code>, then open <code>Task Scheduler</code>.<br/>
Now create a new task and set it to be executed at 3.10AM, we want to make sure the Synology NAS is turned on completely before turning on our PC or it can&#x27;t launch the command to turn on the PC.</p><p><img src="imgs/7.png"/>
<img src="imgs/8.png"/></p><p>Now set the <code>User-defined script</code> to this command which will send a packet to the PC to turn it on.<br/>
<code>synonet --wake 00:00:00:00:00:00 eth0;</code><br/>
Instead of <code>00:00:00:00:00:00</code> you have to set your own PC mac address (search online how to get it).<br/>
You can also set a notification email to know when the PC was turned on to create a backup.<br/></p><p><img src="imgs/9.png"/></p><p>:::warning
Make sure to enable WakeOnLan on your motherboard, search online on how to do that (method changes on every PC).<br/>
:::</p><h3>5. Scheduling automatic shutdown of your PC</h3><p>You have to use my own program in order to schedule an automatic shutdown of your PC after every backup is finished since <strong>Active Backup for Business</strong> Agent lacks of this feature. <br/>
Download my program from my <a href="https://github.com/LoneDev6/ActiveBackupShutdown">Github repo</a> and schedule an automated task to run it on Windows startup.</p><h3>6. Done!</h3><p>I know this tutorial may not be really for beginners but I&#x27;d prefer to avoid spoonfeeding people.<br/>
Good luck with your backups!</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>LoneDev</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/lonedev6</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spam email auto-removal]]></title>
        <id>spam-emails-auto-removal</id>
        <link href="https://blog.devs.beer/blog/spam-emails-auto-removal"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spam emails]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2><img src="icon.png"/> Spam emails</h2><p><img src="imgs/meme.png"/></p><p>If you hate seeing this little number on your Gmail Spam folder, then you will find this article useful.</p><p><img src="imgs/1.png"/></p><p>Sometimes you may receive important emails and they end up being flagged as spam by Gmail, so you probably check this folder daily to make sure no email got mistakely flagged, but you end up seeing:</p><ul><li>meet single Russians</li><li>click here to get 1000$</li><li>your package is going to be delivered, you have to pay the shipping</li><li>and so on...</li></ul><h2>Google Script</h2><ol><li>Visit <a href="https://script.google.com/">script.google.com</a> and create a new <strong>Google Apps Script</strong> for Gmail.</li><li>Choose to create a script for a Blank Project.</li></ol><p><img src="imgs/2.png"/></p><h2>Copying the code</h2><p>Copy and paste this code into the <strong>Code.gs</strong> file (click the <strong>copy</strong> button on the right):</p><details><summary>Click to show the code</summary><p><pre><code class="language-jsx" metastring="title=&quot;Code.js&quot;" title="&quot;Code.js&quot;">  var nice = [
//#region Filter

&quot;storage.googleapis.com/&quot;, // Scams usually use google apis to make their shitty clickable links.

&quot;clevernessoven.com&quot;,
&quot;dissingconnivance.com&quot;,
&quot;vuroc.com&quot;,
&quot;siatave.com&quot;,
&quot;1dznhmvbvg-------------------------.com &quot;,
&quot;lxuagolwx.us&quot;,
&quot;unionsecret.com&quot;,
&quot;redeemsexcavate.com&quot;,
&quot;wuszofvbw.us&quot;,
&quot;augustdot.com&quot;,
&quot;xhmdefmwyvniad.org&quot;,
&quot;scorchedca.eu.org&quot;,
&quot;ipptr.com&quot;,
&quot;ip-pool.com&quot;,
&quot;cryptcapitalgroup.com&quot;,
&quot;attentivenessfeather.com&quot;,
&quot;titansvision.com&quot;,
&quot;digitalincome24x7.com&quot;,
&quot;stockscapitalgroup.com&quot;,
&quot;war7xg31l--.com&quot;,
&quot;infancyboy.com&quot;,
&quot;dreamsatisfaction.com&quot;,
&quot;serverclienti.com&quot;,
&quot;coppel.com&quot;,
&quot;larkbutterfly.com&quot;,
&quot;divestaxiom.com&quot;,
&quot;thebtcinvestment.com&quot;,
&quot;ljciyzhupg-----------pgbuek-.com&quot;,
&quot;exchangevisitcompany.com&quot;,
&quot;pgbuek-.com&quot;,
&quot;bruntheavy.com&quot;,
&quot;mail-getresponse.com&quot;,
&quot;sharepointonline.com&quot;,
&quot;faycushion.com&quot;,
&quot;ikexpress.com&quot;,
&quot;jcom.zaq.ne.jp&quot;,
&quot;key-data.co.uk&quot;,
&quot;vwyorfr.us&quot;,
&quot;qgdahhw.us&quot;,
&quot;pnkqrev.us&quot;,
&quot;wlnnnxx.us&quot;,
&quot;friendlycabochon.com&quot;,
&quot;naiado.com&quot;,
&quot;emails-jobsdelivered.com&quot;,
&quot;bvdxuzt.us&quot;,
&quot;perrychristinejacobs.work&quot;,
&quot;gpxxpdx.us&quot;,
&quot;boxingsuit.org.uk&quot;,
&quot;independantnewspaper.de&quot;,
&quot;arqxkhu.us&quot;,
&quot;flutterfleapit.com&quot;,
&quot;wg6ur8-.com&quot;,
&quot;5nakhak5x.us&quot;,
&quot;riskchemicalproduct.org.uk&quot;,
&quot;bestclassicmusic.org.uk&quot;,
&quot;planningbrands.com&quot;,
&quot;alpha-lt.net&quot;,
&quot;amorphousanimus.com&quot;,

&quot;Franklin Ave Ste&quot;,
&quot;123 SE 3rd Ave. Suite 574, Miami&quot;,
&quot;5960 South Land Park&quot;,
&quot;Tvrdého 643 19900 Praha 9&quot;,
&quot;928 S Dixie Hwy&quot;,
&quot;34 N Franklin Ave Ste&quot;,
&quot;Long Prairie Rd&quot;,
&quot;Alicia Pkwy&quot;,
&quot;Laguna Niguel&quot;,

&quot;CITIBANK&quot;,
&quot;Your Bank name&quot;,
&quot;𝐩𝐫𝐨𝐬𝐭𝐚𝐭𝐞&quot;, // LOL

&quot;LinkedIn Corporation&quot;
//#endregion
];


//#region Logic
function filterViaSpam() 
{
  var threads = GmailApp.getSpamThreads(0, 30);
  for (var i = 0; i &lt; threads.length; i++) 
  {
    var messages=threads[i].getMessages();
    for (var j = 0; j &lt; messages.length; j++) 
    {
      var message=messages[j];
      var body=message.getRawContent();
      if(check(body, nice))
      {
        GmailApp.moveThreadToTrash(threads[i]);
        console.log(&quot;Found: &quot; + message.getSubject());
      }
      Utilities.sleep(1000);
    }
  }
}
function check(body, arr)
{
  for (var i = 0; i &lt; arr.length; i++) 
  { 
    if(body.indexOf(arr[i]) &gt;- 1)
      return true;
  }
  return false;
}
//#endregion

</code></pre></p></details><p>This code also includes a predefined set of rules I created during time.</p><h2>Automatically trigger the check</h2><p>Now click the stopwatch icon to set an automatic trigger for the previous code. </p><p><img src="imgs/3.png"/></p><p>And set the form values as I did.</p><p><img src="imgs/4.png"/></p><h2>Done, you&#x27;re free!</h2><p>Finally you can make sure only mistakely spam-marked can go into the Spam folder.<br/>
Most scam emails will be automatically deleted each 10 minutes. </p><br/><br/><br/> Sources:<br/><p><a href="https://www.geektron.com/2014/01/how-to-filter-gmail-using-email-headers-and-stop-via-spam/">geektron.com</a></p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>LoneDev</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/lonedev6</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of ItemsAdder]]></title>
        <id>future-of-itemsadder</id>
        <link href="https://blog.devs.beer/blog/future-of-itemsadder"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ItemsAdder]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>ItemsAdder</h2><p><a href="https://www.spigotmc.org/resources/73355/">ItemsAdder</a> is my most successful product. It&#x27;s a plugin for <a href="https://www.spigotmc.org/">Spigot</a> servers which allows admins to extend the game without modding the client.</p><h2>First days</h2><p>The plugin was published initially on 2016 and was called <strong>NewItems</strong>, it was one of my very first Java projects and I was a newbie on Spigot development.<br/>
I abandoned the old project after a year or so due to personal life, but then I picked it back up and started working on the very new version which ended up begin renamed ItemsAdder. As you know this version has more features, has a totally different structure and allows to achieve extreme customization of the game.</p><h2>Current days</h2><p>I didn&#x27;t expect this much fame for that single product, the <a href="https://pstats.devs.beer/plugin/bukkit/ItemsAdder/6">max peak</a> of servers which use ItemsAdder amounts to <strong>1097 max online servers</strong> and <strong>3800 max players</strong> enjoying the plugin.<br/>
ItemsAdder is in the <a href="https://i.imgur.com/m3edZ8T.png">top 3</a> of the best voted paid Spigot plugins to this date, which is unbelievable, a plugin published in 2019 managed to reach the top 3 in 2 years while the forum itself is online since 2012.</p><p>Currently my main efforts are to maintain the most stable and optimized code as possible because this plugin is used on servers with more than 100 players connected, performance is a priority in these cases.</p><p>The most difficult task is to give support to customers because a lot of them find it easier to contact me without reading the official tutorials nor asking to the other community members and this sadly cuts a lot of the development time.
I&#x27;d love to spend more time on actually coding the plugin.<br/>
Sadly most of them blackmail me with 1 star reviews which is making this situation really hard to maintain in the long term. </p><h2>The future</h2><p>Back in the day I rushed a lot of ItemsAdder features initial planning, this resulted in non-balanced default stats and gameplay, this is why I&#x27;m currently working with some friends to rebalance the default items pack and provide a better gameplay.<br/>
This is a very long task due to the fact that this plugin offers more than 500 default items/materials/blocks but I&#x27;ll do my best to release an updated pack before mid 2022.<br/>
I also plan to hook into the Minecraft gameplay itself and fix all the unbalanced features of the vanilla gameplay. Sadly this game has a lot of flaws which allow users to <a href="https://www.speedrun.com/mc/run/zq13899m">speedrun it in no time</a>.</p><p>One of the last important tasks I have scheduled is to find a proper way to avoid spamming customers which are contacting me everyday to ask basic questions. Right now I have no solution as this is the problem every developer has with this community.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>LoneDev</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/lonedev6</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[⚡ Optimize Minecraft client]]></title>
        <id>optimize-minecraft</id>
        <link href="https://blog.devs.beer/blog/optimize-minecraft"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft is slow]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Minecraft is slow</h2><p>:::info
<strong>Minecraft</strong> is known to be very heavy, the community had fixed most of its problems.<br/>
My plugins don&#x27;t require this mod. This is an optional tutorial for who wants to optimize their game, because it is slow.
:::</p><h3>1. Downloading Fabric</h3><p>First you have to <a href="https://fabricmc.net/use/">download</a> <strong>Fabric</strong> and install it.<br/>
Click on the &quot;<strong>Download installer</strong>&quot; button:</p><p><img src="imgs/1.png"/></p><h3>2. Edit the profile folder (optional step)</h3><p>Click on &quot;<strong>installations</strong>&quot;, then press on &quot;<strong>edit</strong>&quot; under the &quot;<strong>Fabric</strong>&quot; installation.</p><p><img src="imgs/3.png"/></p><p>Change the folder to a new one, for example I created a new profile folder called <code>Fabric</code> inside <code>.minecraft</code>.</p><p><img src="imgs/4.png"/></p><h3>3. Install the optimization mod</h3><p>Download the mod <a href="https://www.curseforge.com/minecraft/modpacks/fabulously-optimized/files/">here</a>.<br/></p><p>:::warning
Select your version and make sure to download the &quot;MultiMC&quot; type.
:::</p><p>Open the zip and extract the folders <code>mods</code> and <code>config</code> inside your <code>.minecraft</code> folder (or inside the <strong>Fabric</strong> profile folder).</p><h3>4. Run Fabric</h3>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>LoneDev</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/lonedev6</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>